What things make you laugh?
什么事物会让你发笑？
There are many things that make us chuckle or burst into laughter.
生活中有很多事情能让我们忍不住轻笑或是捧腹大笑。
This natural show of emotion gives off signals that we are happy, we find something humorous or even that we’re just a barrel of laughs!
这种自然的情绪表达会传递出我们很开心、觉得某件事很有趣，甚至我们是开心果的信号！
Gelotologists have been looking at why we do it and what the benefits are.
笑学家们一直在研究人类发笑的原因以及笑能带来的益处。
Laughter is a very primitive way of making a sound.
笑是一种非常原始的发声方式。
When we do it, we make very strange noises – from wheezes and squeaks to gasps and snorts – and each sound simply reflects the muscles in the chest squeezing out air from our ribcages under very high pressure.
当我们笑的时候，会发出各种奇怪的声音——从喘息声、尖细的笑声到倒吸气声、鼻息声都有，每一种声音都源于胸腔肌肉在高压下将空气挤出胸腔的过程。
Most of the time our laughter is involuntary and contagious, particularly between friends.
大多数时候，我们的笑是无意识且具有感染力的，在朋友之间尤其如此。
Neuroscientist, Sophie Scott, told the BBC that it’s “a social emotion.
神经科学家索菲·斯科特在接受BBC采访时表示，笑“是一种社交性的情绪。
It’s better to laugh with people we like.”
和自己喜欢的人一起笑，会更愉悦”。
She defines two types of laughter – spontaneous laughter, where we laugh instantly and uncontrollably, and conversational laughter – where we laugh together with friends.
她将笑分为两种类型——自发性的笑，也就是那种不由自主、瞬间爆发的笑，以及交谈式的笑，即和朋友们一起时产生的笑声。
Research found, on average, people laugh seven times for every ten minutes of conversation.
研究发现，人们平均每十分钟的对话中就会笑七次。
The BBC World Service programme Crowd Science examined the science of laughter.
英国广播公司全球服务节目《大众科学》探究了笑的科学原理。
It wanted to know what caused this highly infectious repetitive action.
该节目试图找出这种极具感染力的重复性行为背后的原因。
It found we use laughter to show others that we’re being playful and non-threatening, and this serves to make and maintain social bonds.
研究发现，我们通过笑向他人传递出“我们在开玩笑，没有恶意”的信号，这有助于建立和维系社交关系。
Also, people outside of our social group can understand the relationship between the laughers by the sound of our chuckles.
此外，社交圈子之外的人也能通过笑声的特点，判断出发笑者之间的关系。
While our health is no laughing matter, research has found a good guffaw can help our body and mind – it can make us feel good and relax our bodies. It also helps us manage pain and improve our immune system.
虽然健康问题绝非儿戏，但研究发现，开怀大笑对我们的身心都大有裨益——它能让我们心情愉悦，放松身体，还有助于缓解疼痛、增强免疫系统。
That’s why laughter therapy is being used as an alternative to conventional treatments.
这也是为什么笑声疗法正被用作传统疗法的替代方案。
But generally, our ability to laugh is out of our control.
不过通常来说，我们发笑的本能是不受控制的。
When you start doing it, just go with the flow and others will join in.
当你笑起来的时候，只管顺其自然，身边的人自然会跟着一起笑。